businesswebbasics.com 2016-07-30

# PRIVACY POLICY - Business Web Basics

Privacy

PREMAZON INTERNET BUSINESS CONSULTING, BUSINESS WEB BASICS AND ANN PREMAZON want to make your online experience satisfying and safe. We want to provide you with the means to control your privacy and give you a way to voice questions or concerns you may have.

We sometimes collect non identifiable information from visits to our Web sites to help us provide better customer service. For example, we keep track of the domains from which people visit, and we also measure visitor activity on PREMAZON INTERNET BUSINESS CONSULTING, BUSINESS WEB BASICS AND ANN PREMAZON Web sites, but we do so in ways that keep the information non identifiable.

Also, when we collect personal data from you in a transaction, we may extract some information about that transaction in an non identifiable format and combine it with other non identifiable information such as clickstream data. This information is used and analyzed only at an aggregate level to help us understand trends and patterns. This information is not reviewed at an individual level. If you do not want your transaction details used in this manner you can disable your cookies.

We collect the information we mentioned in the previous paragraphs through the use of various technologies, including one called “cookies”. A cookie is a piece of data that a Web site can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your computer as an anonymous tag that identifies your computer but not you. Some PREMAZON INTERNET BUSINESS CONSULTING, BUSINESS WEB BASICS AND ANN PREMAZON pages use cookies, sent by PREMAZON INTERNET BUSINESS CONSULTING, BUSINESS WEB BASICS AND ANN PREMAZON or its third party vendors, or other technologies to better serve you when you return to the Web site. You can set your browser to notify you before you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. You can also set your browser to turn off cookies. If you do so, however, some Web sites may not work properly. Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies.

If you turn off cookies, other technologies will still detect visits to these pages, but the notices they generate cannot be associated with other non identifiable cookie information and are disregarded.

Information Distribution

It is our strict policy not to share your personal information or preferences with any third party, except as is necessary to operate and improve our website, or to provide any service requested by you on our website.

Although unlikely, we may be required by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide personally identifiable information to the appropriate governmental authorities. If requested as part of a legal proceeding, we will provide this information upon receipt of the appropriate documentation.

It is not our usual policy but from time to time we may permit other companies to place advertising on our website, and these companies may collect information about you through the use of cookies when you view or click on their advertising or content (using the same techniques described above). Due to the way the Internet operates, we cannot control this collection of information. You should contact these advertisers or content providers if you have any questions about their use of the information they collect.

There may be links that will let you leave our website. Except for Web sites directly related to PREMAZON INTERNET BUSINESS CONSULTING, BUSINESS WEB BASICS AND ANN PREMAZON programs and services, we cannot control the links or their Web sites and we are not responsible for the contents of any linked website or any link contained in a linked website. The inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement of the website. The use and/or privacy provided by a linked website as to any information you provide in accessing that website is in no way subject to our privacy policy. Any linked website may have its own policy that could differ considerably from our policy, or the linked website may not display any privacy policy at all. In any case, even though a linked website is accessed through our website, we cannot be responsible for any use that a linked website may make of your information.

Your Acceptance of These Terms

By using this site, you agree to our Privacy Policy. We may also change the policy from time to time, so please be sure to visit this site often to see if anything has changed. If we post changes and you continue to use the site, you will be deemed to have agreed to the changes.
